<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dihara Wijetunga</title>
    <link>https://diharaw.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dihara Wijetunga</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:52:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://diharaw.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Hybrid Rendering</title>
      <link>https://diharaw.github.io/post/adventures_in_hybrid_rendering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 22:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diharaw.github.io/post/adventures_in_hybrid_rendering/</guid>
      <description>As an accompanying piece to my recently released Hybrid Rendering sample, this blog post dives into some of the techniques and optimizations used and will help anyone interested to understand the project.
Before going any further let&amp;rsquo;s answer the question &amp;ldquo;Why hybrid rendering?&amp;rdquo;. In a typical rasterization based rendering pipeline, certain effects such as Global Illumination, Reflections and Soft Shadows have to be approximated using either screen space techniques, offline baking or other approaches which typically lead to less-than-believable results in many cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://diharaw.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diharaw.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Dihara Wijetunga - Graphics Programmer  Summary  Graphics Programmer 5+ years of work experience with a keen interest in high-end rendering techniques and real-time ray-tracing for video games, low-level optimization and game engine programming.
 Technical Skills   C/C++, Rust, Vulkan, DirectX 12, OpenGL, Rendering Techniques and Architecture, Real-time Ray-Tracing and Denoising, Physically Based Rendering, Global Illumination, Shader and Rendering Optimization, Profiling and Debugging Tools, Unity, Unreal Engine 4, Lumberyard/O3DE   Work Experience  Developer Technology Engineer 2, July 2019 - Present</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://diharaw.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diharaw.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a graphics programmer from Sri Lanka currently working as a Developer Technology Engineer at Imagination Technologies in the United Kingdom. I have experience in developing high-end rendering techniques and doing low-level performance optimizations on PC and mobile platforms. I enjoy problem-solving on complex codebases and I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about learning the latest and greatest graphics techniques and like to dabble in all aspects of game engine programming.
My main skillset includes proficiency with with C/C++ and multithreading, knowledge of advanced real-time rendering techniques, ray-tracing, low-level graphics APIs and experience with GPU profiling and optimization using tools such as RenderDoc, PIX and Nsight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://diharaw.github.io/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://diharaw.github.io/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Helios
Hybrid Rendering
GPU Particle System
FFT Ocean Waves
Lightmaps
Runtime IBL
Rasterator
Deferred Decals
Animation Systems
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
